http://www.brainstormworld.com/About/privacy_policy

Privacy Policy
(Updated May 23, 2018)
How do you use my personal information?
Your personal information is entered into our system (by you) when you contact us. This information is only used as contact information regarding your work. No one can see or have access to your personal information, such as your name, address and phone number. Your personal information is never shared with a third party, and it is against our privacy policy to do so.
The image uploaded to apply the Artistic effect (by you) on cloud would be removed immediately from our server in case of success or failure.
We do not use any analytics or ad networks on our website.
Can I opt in or opt out of your mailing list for unwanted emails?
Should you ever receive anything other than an automated email regarding your query or an email from management concerning any questions we may have about your work, please contact us and ask to be removed from our mailing list. We will take immediate action.
How do you use my audio materials?
Your audio materials are used for transcription purposes only. The audios are used solely by the transcriptionists who type up the audio, after which they are deleted from our database. As mentioned above, all typists are required to sign a legally binding Confidentiality/ND Agreement with us upon hire. You can be guaranteed that all audio materials will not be shared with any third party. It is against our privacy policy to do so.
How will I know if there are privacy policy changes?
Should we make any additions or deletions to this privacy policy, we will not contact you; however, you may check this page at any time and note the last date of update for comparison.
What if I have more questions concerning your privacy policy?
If you have any further questions concerning our privacy policy, please
contact us.
